Guide to the Sydney Howard Gay Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Locke, David R. (Box 45)
  - Locke, Mary T (Box 45)
  - Locke, Mary S (Box 45)
  - Lockerby, A.P. (Box 45)
  - Lockwood, Joseph E (Box 45)
  - Loring, Stella L (Box 45)
  - Lovett (Box 45)
  - Low, John (Box 45)
  - Lowell, Charles (Box 45)
  - Lowell, James Russell, 1819-1891 (Box 45)
  - Lowell, Josephine Shaw, 1843-1905 (Box 45)
  - Lowell, Marie (White), 1821-1853 (Box 45)
  - Lucas, Mrs (Box 45)
  - Ludlow, William H (Box 45)
  - Ludlum, Rebecca M (Box 45)
  - Lukens, Anna (Box 45)
  - Lupton, John (Box 45)
  - Lyman, J.H. (Box 45)
  - Lyman, Susan J (Box 45)
  - Lyng (?), Charles D. (Box 45)
  - McAtee, Morton S (Box 46)
  - McClintock, Elizabeth (See also: Phillips, E.) (Box 46)
  - McClintock, Mary A. (Mrs. Thomas) (Box 46)
  - McClintock, Sarah (Box 46)
  - McClintock, Thomas (Box 46)
  - McConnell, Henry Lloyd (Box 46)
  - McConnell, Luther W (Box 46)
  - McCoy, Joseph H (Box 46)
  - McCulloch, Hugh 1808-1895 (Box 46)
  - McGehn, Miles C (Box 46)
  - McGinnis, Catherine (Box 46)
  - McGregor, W.D. (Box 46)
  - McIntyre,J. (Box 46)
  - McKee, Nora L (Box 46)
  - McKenna, John L (Box 46)
  - Mackensie, Alexander (Box 46)
  - Mackenzie, Robert Shelton, 1809-1880 (Box 46)
  - Mackie, James S (Box 46)
  - McKim, James Miller (Box 46)
  - McKim, Sarah A (Box 46)
  - Mackie, James (Box 46)
  - MacManus, F.E. (Box 47)
  - McMaster, James Alphonsus, 1820-1886 (Box 47)
  - McWatters, George S (Box 47)
  - Macy, Charles A (Box 47)
  - Macy, Francis H. Jr. (Box 47)
  - Maginnis, J.S (Box 47)
  - Mallory, Sarah (Box 47)
  - Manly, M G (Box 47)
  - Marsh, O.C. (Box 47)
  - Mann, Daniel S (Box 47)
  - Mann, Horace (Box 47)
  - Marshall, J.N. (Box 47)
  - Martineau, Harriet, 1802-1876 (Box 47)
  - Mason, James M. (Box 47)
  - Massachusetts Anti-Slavery Society (Box 47)
  - Massie, Mrs. (Box 47)
  - Matthews, Dr. (Box 47)
  - Maxwell, Sidney D (Box 47)
  - May, Elizabeth G (Box 47)
  - May, Samuel, Jr. (Box 48)
  - Mayers, Sydney (Box 48)
  - Mayhew, Jonathan, 1720-1766 (Box 48)
  - Meade, George Gordon, 1815-1872 (Box 48)
  - Meach, Walton (Box 48)
  - Means, Paul B. (Box 48)
  - Meeker, N.C. (Box 48)
  - Meigs, Charles A (Box 48)
  - Meigs, Henry (Box 48)
  - Melvill, John (Box 48)
  - Mendenhall, Ellwood (Box 48)
  - Mercier, Henri (Box 48)
  - Mesla, I.M. (Box 48)
  - Metford, Phoebe (Box 48)
  - Mickly, N (Box 48)
  - Mifflin, Lloyd, 1846-1921 (Box 48)
  - Mifflin, Sarah (Box 48)
  - Mifflin, Warner (Box 48)
  - Miles, Pliny (?) (Box 48)
  - Millar, Willson (Box 48)
  - Millar, Willson (Box 48)
  - Mills, Harriet May (Box 48)
  - Milner, Julius (Box 48)
  - Minod, H (Box 48)
  - Minot, Hattie (Box 48)
  - Mix, Simon H (Box 48)
  - Moore, Frank (Box 48)
  - Moore, George H (Box 48)
  - Moore, Lily (Box 48)
  - Moorhead, James (Box 48)
  - Morgan, Edwin Dennison, 1811-1883 (Box 48)
  - Morgan, Eugene, Jr. (Box 48)
  - Morgan, James Appleton (Box 48)
  - Morgan, Thomas S (Box 48)
  - Morris, E (Box 48)
  - Morse, John T., Jr. (Box 48)
  - Morton, A.D. (Box 48)
  - Mosby, John S (Box 48)
  - Mott, James (Box 48)
  - Mott, Lucretia Coffin, 1793-1880 (Box 48)
  - Mott, Lydia P. (Box 48)
  - Mudd, I.H. Clay (Box 48)
  - Murphy, Henry C (Box 48)
  - Murrow, W.J. (Box 49)
  - Nagai, K. (Box 49)
  - Neall, A.V. (Box 49)
  - Neall, Cecelia A. (Mrs. Daniel, Jr.) (Box 49)
  - Neall, Daniel (Box 49)
  - Neall, Daniel, Jr, 1849 (Box 49)
  - Neall, Daniel, Jr, 1850- (Box 50)
  - Neall, Frank L (Box 50)
  - Neall, Rebecca Bunker (Box 50)
  - Neall, Wilhelmina (Mrs. Frank L.) (Box 50)
  - Needless, Augusta (Box 50)
  - Nelson, Catherine H. (Box 50)
  - Newbold, E[Iizabeth] J. (Box 50)
  - Newbould, Thomas (Box 50)
  - Newcomb, J. Warren (Box 51)
  - Nicerun, E.E. (Box 51)
  - Nicholson, Valentine (Box 51)
  - Nimbury, E.W. (Box 51)
  - Nordhoff, Charles, 1830-1901 (Box 51)
  - Nutter, Richard N (Box 51)
  - Oakey, S.M. (Box 51)
  - O'Conor, Charles 1804-1884 (Box 51)
  - Olcott, H.S. (Box 51)
  - Olmsted, Frederick Law, 1822-1903 (Box 51)
  - O'Relly, Henry, 1806-1886 (Box 51)
  - Osgood, James Ripley, 1836-1892 (Box 51)
  - Otis, Amos (Box 51)
  - Otis, J. (Box 51)
  - Otis, John Alexander (Box 51)
  - Otis, John, 1774-1854 (Box 51)
  - Otis, M.Z. (Box 51)
  - Otis, Nathaniel W (Box 51)
  - Otis, Walter M (Box 51)
  - Ottarson, Franklin J (Box 51)
  - Owen, Robert (Box 51)
  - Owen, Robert Dale 1801-1877 (Box 51)
  - Oyarzahal, George (Box 51)
  - Oxholm, Lucile H (Box 51)
  - Page, Charles Anderson (Box 51)
  - Page, Henrietta (Box 51)
  - Page, R.C.M. (Box 51)
  - Paige, Nathaniel (Box 51)
  - Paine, Seth (Box 51)
  - Painter, Uriah H (Box 51)
  - Palfrey, John Gorham, 1796-1881 (Box 51)
  - Palmer, Henrietta L. (Mrs John W.) (Box 51)
  - Palmer, John Williamson, 1825-1906 (Box 52)
  - Parker, Theodore, 1810-1860 (Box 52)
  - Parkman, J (Box 52)
  - Parkman, Susan. (Box 52)
  - Parmelle, A B (Box 52)
  - Parmelle, Samuel N (Box 52)
  - Parsons, Anna O.T. (Box 52)
  - Parsons, Caroline L (Box 52)
  - Parsons, Timothy (Box 52)
  - Paton, Andrew (Box 52)
  - Patton, Ludlow (Box 52)
  - Pease, Elizabeth (Box 52)
  - Pease, H.F. (Box 52)
  - Pelly, J (Box 52)
  - Pennock, Joseph Siddon (Box 52)
  - Perkins, William (Box 52)
  - Phelps, George D., etc. (Box 52)
  - Philip, Mary Potter (Box 52)
  - Phillips, Ann (Box 52)
  - Phillips, Elizabeth McClintock (see also: McC--, E.) (Box 52)
  - Phillips, Wendell (1811-1884), 1845 (Box 52)
  - Phillips, Wendell (1811-1884), 1846-1892 (Box 53)
  - Platt, Donn (Box 53)
  - Pickard, Samuel Thomas, 1828-1915 (Box 54)
  - Pickering, Octavius (Box 54)
  - Pierce, Moses (Box 54)
  - Pierpont, John, 1785-1866 (Box 54)
  - Pike, Charles E (Box 54)
  - Pillsbury, Parker, 1809-1898 (Box 54)
  - Plantz, Homer G. (Box 54)
  - Plumly, B. Rush (Box 54)
  - Pollard, Agnes L (Box 54)
  - Pollard, Edith N (Box 54)
  - Pollard, Edward Alfred, 1831-1872 (Box 54)
  - Porter, Burr (Box 54)
  - Porter, Fitz-John, 1822-1901 (Box 54)
  - Porter, Susan (?) (Box 54)
  - Post, Alice Thacher (Mrs. Louis F.) (Box 54)
  - Post, T.A. (Box 54)
  - Potter, John H (Box 54)
  - Potter, M.D. (Box 54)
  - Powell, Anna (Rice), 1855 (Box 54)
  - Powell, Aaron Macy, 1832-1899 (Box 54A)
  - Powell, Anna (Rice), undated (Box 55)
  - Prentiss, M. (?) (Box 55)
  - Pryor, George C. (Box 55)
  - Pugh, E.K. (Box 56)
  - Pugh, Sarah, 1855 (Box 56)
  - Pugh, Sarah, 1856-1884 & undated (Box 57)
  - Puleston, J.H. (Box 57)
  - Pullar, John (Box 57)
  - Purvis, Annie M. (Box 57)
  - Purvis, H (Box 57)
  - Purvis, Robert (Box 57)
  - Putnam, George Palmer 1814-1872 (Box 57)
  - Putnam, George W. (Box 57)
  - Quincy, Edmund (1808-1877), 1852 (Box 58)
  - Quincy, Edmund (1808-1877), 1853-1873 (Box 58A)
  - Quincy, Edmund, Jr. (Box 58A)
  - Quincy, Josiah, 1772-1864 (Box 58A)
  - Quincy, Mary (Box 58A)
  - Rathbun, George K. (Box 58A)
  - Ramsey, Alex (Box 58A)
  - Rathburn, George (Box 58A)
  - Raymond, Henry Jarvis, 1820-1869 (Box 58A)
  - Redden, Laura Catherine, 1840-1923 (Box 58A)
  - Redpath, James, 1833-1891 (Box 58A)
  - Reed, William Bradford, 1806-1876 (Box 58A)
  - Reed, William Bradford, 1806-1876 (Box 58A)
  - Reid, E.J. (Box 58A)
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1837-1912 (Box 58A)
  - Remond,Charles Lenox, 1810-1873 (Box 58A)
  - Reynolds, Benjamin (Box 58A)
  - Reynolds, M.W. (Box 58A)
  - Reynolds, Thomas C (Box 58A)
  - Rhoads, Samuel (Box 58A)
  - Rice, A.I. (Box 58A)
  - Rich, John F (Box 58A)
  - Richards, A.C. (Box 58A)
  - Richardson, Abby Sage McFarland (Box 58A)
  - Richardson, Albert Deane (Box 59)
  - Richardson, Anna M (Box 60)
  - Richardson, Charles Addison (Box 60)
  - Richardson, Mary Louise Pease (Mrs. Albert D.) (Box 60)
  - Rickertson, Daniel (Box 60)
  - Rickertson, Joseph (Box 60)
  - Ring, Thomas O. (Box 60)
  - Ripley, George, 1802-1880 (Box 60)
  - Ritter, W.H. (Box 60)
  - Robinson, William Stevens, 1818-1876 (Box 60)
  - Rogers, Eliza S (Box 60)
  - Rogers, N.P. (Box 60)
  - Rogers, S (Box 60)
  - Rollins, John A (Box 60)
  - Rooker, Thomas N. (Box 60)
  - Runkle, Lucia Gilbert (Box 60)
  - Russell, G.R. (Box 60)
  - Russell, John E (Box 60)
  - Russell, Ruth (Box 60)
  - Saint Anthoine, Hippolyte de (Box 60)
  - Salisbury, Albert, 1843-1911 (Box 60)
  - Sanders, George Nichlas, 1812-1873 (Box 60)
  - Sands, Louis (Box 60)
  - Sanford, E.S (Box 60)
  - Sargent, George B (Box 60)
  - Sargent, Henrietta (Box 60)
  - Savage, I.Y. Jr. (Box 60)
  - Savage, William (Box 60)
  - Scammon, J. Young (Box 60)
  - Schem, Alexander Jacob (Box 60)
  - Schurz, Carl, 1829-1906 (Box 60)
  - Scollay, John (Box 60)
  - Scott, Genio C. (Box 60)
  - Scribner, Charles, 1854-1930 (Box 60)
  - Scribner, J. Blair (Box 60)
  - Scribner's Charles and Sons (Box 60)
  - Scudder, Horace Ellisha, 1826-1906 (Box 60)
  - Searing, Laura see: Redden, Laura (Box 60)
  - Sedgwick, D.W. (Box 60)
  - Serrell, Colonel (Box 60)
  - Sewall, S.E. (Box 60)
  - Sewall, S.E. (Box 60)
  - Seybold, Thad. S (Box 60)
  - Seybold, Thad. S. (Box 60)
  - Seymour, Almira (Box 60)
  - Seymour, Edward (Box 60)
  - Seymour, J.C.W. (Box 60)
  - St. Clair, Alanson (Box 60)
  - Shaffer, J.W. (Box 61)
  - Shakelton, Mary (Box 61)
  - Shapter, P. (Box 61)
  - Shaw, Frank George, 1809-1882 (Box 61)
  - Shaw, Gardiner Howland (Box 61)
  - Shaw, Sarah B (Box 61)
  - Shea, George (Box 61)
  - Sheahan, J.W. (Box 61)
  - Shea, John Gilvary, 1824-1892 (Box 61)
  - Sheibleson (?) Mary (Box 61)
  - Shelley, Richard L. (Box 61)
  - Shepherd, Nathaniel G (Box 61)
  - Sherman, Anne (Box 61)
  - Sherman, William Tecumsh (Box 61)
  - Shore, W.W. (Box 62)
  - Shriver, Edward J (Box 62)
  - Sigel, Franz (Box 62)
  - Sikes, William Wirt, 1836-1883 (Box 62)
  - Simner, Lucy (Box 62)
  - Simonson, May S. (Box 62)
  - Sinclair, Samuel (Box 62)
  - Smalley, George W., July, 1862 (Box 62)
  - Smalley, George W., August, 1862-1871 (Box 63)
  - Smith, Elias, 1862 (Box 63)
  - Smith, Gerrit, 1797­1874 (Box 64)
  - Smith, Increase S (Box 64)
  - Smith, James M'Cune (Box 64)
  - Smith, Myra R (Box 64)
  - Smith R (Box 64)
  - Smith, William Prescott (Box 64)
  - Snodgrass, J.E. (Box 64)
  - Snow, [Luther?] (Box 64)
  - Snyder, George (Box 64)
  - Sparks, Jared, 1789-1866 (Box 64)
  - Spooner, Lysander, 1808-1887 (Box 64)
  - Squier, Ephraim, George l821-1888 (Box 64)
  - Stahel, Julius (Box 64)
  - Stanton, Edwin McMasters, 1814-1869 (Box 64)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth (Cady), 1815-1902 (Box 64)
  - Stanton, Henry Brewster, 1805-1887 (Box 64)
  - Staples, E.D. (Box 64)
  - Staples, J.B. (Box 64)
  - Stebbins, Giles B (Box 64)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, 1833-1908 (Box 64)
  - Stetson, C. (Box 64)
  - Stevens, George L (Box 64)
  - Stevens, H.L. (Box 64)
  - Stevens, Obediah (Box 64)
  - Stewart, D.H (Box 64)
  - Sticker, Sarah (Box 64)
  - Stickney, Albert (Box 64)
  - Stickney, L.D. (Box 64)
  - Stiles, Edward (Box 64)
  - Stoddard, Moses (Box 64)
  - Stoddard, Richard Henry, 1825-1903 (Box 64)
  - Stone, Thomas T (Box 64)
  - Stone, William L (Box 64)
  - Stone, William Wetmore, l8l9-l895 (Box 64)
  - Stratton, Caroline (Box 64)
  - Sturgis, James (Box 64)
  - Stryker, William S (Box 64)
  - Suliot, T.E. (Box 64)
  - Sullivan, John (Box 64)
  - Sullivan, M.A. (Box 64)
  - Sumner, Charles, 1811-1874 (Box 64)
  - Swaine, I (Box 64)
  - Sypher, Josiah Rhinehart (Box 64)
  - Sypher, Josiah Rhinehart, May 1863 (Box 65)
  - Talbot, George Foster (Box 65)
  - Tappan, Lewis (Box 65)
  - Tarbell, Sewall (Box 65)
  - Taylor, Bayard, l825-l878 (Box 65)
  - Taylor, Edward (Box 65)
  - Taylor, James B (Box 65)
  - Thaxter, Anna Q (Box 65)
  - Thaxter, Edward (Box 65)
  - Thaxter, John Q (Box 65)
  - Thomas, R.G. (Box 65)
  - Thompson, George, 1804-1878 (Box 65)
  - Thompson, Henry (Box 65)
  - Thurston, James (Box 65)
  - Tidmarsh, Mary T (Box 65)
  - Tilton, Theodore, 1835-1907 (Box 65)
  - Tims, Hannah Sophia (Box 65)
  - Tommy, Pete (Box 65)
  - Toney, L.B. (Box 65)
  - Tonnsene, Thomas S (Box 65)
  - Torrey, Charles Turner, 1813-1846 (Box 65)
  - Torry, Henry Warren 1814-1893 (Box 65)
  - Towne, Henrietta (Box 65)
  - Townsend, George Alfred, 1841-1914 (Box 65)
  - Townesend, Tacie (Box 65)
  - Train, George Francis, 1829-1904 (Box 65)
  - Treadway, Rosalind (Box 65)
  - Trumbull, James Hammond, 1821-1897 (Box 65)
  - Tuckerman, E.W. (Box 65)
  - Tuxbury, Helen (Box 65)
  - Tweedy, E (Box 65)
  - Tyler, George W (Box 65)
  - Tyng, Charles Y (Box 65)
  - Tyng, Stephen Higginson, 1800-1881 (Box 65)
  - Van Wyck, C.H. (Box 65)
  - Vaine, S.W. (Box 65)
  - Underwood, Francis Henry, 1825-1894 (Box 65)
  - Vaughn, M.C. (Box 65)
  - Villard, Henry (Box 66)
  - Vines, Mrs, Hannah (Box 66)
  - Visscher, S.G. (Box 66)
  - Wade, John (Box 66)
  - Wade, William (Box 66)
  - Waldo, L.F. (Box 66)
  - Walker, George E (Box 66)
  - Walker, Jonathan, 1799-1878 (Box 66)
  - Wallcut, Robert F (Box 66)
  - Waller, Estelle (Box 66)
  - Walser, Eleanor E (Box 66)
  - Walter, Joseph R. (Box 66)
  - Walton, E.H (Box 66)
  - Ward, G.A. (Box 66)
  - Ward, George C. (Box 66)
  - Ward, James C (Box 66)
  - Ward, M.A. (Box 66)
  - Ward, S.A. (Box 66)
  - Ward, W.A. (Box 66)
  - Waring, George E. (Box 66)
  - Warrne, Winslow, 1838-1930 (Box 66)
  - Warner, Charles Dudley, 1829-1900 (Box 66)
  - Watson, Winslow Marston (Box 66)
  - Webb, Hannah (Box 66)
  - Webb, John (Box 66)
  - Webb, Richard Davis, 1805-1872 (Box 67)
  - Webster, Albert L (Box 67)
  - Webster, Daniel (Box 67)
  - Webster, Mary L (Box 67)
  - Weed, Samuel R. (Box 67)
  - Weidemeyer, J.W. (Box 67)
  - Weir, L.C. (Box 67)
  - Weisenhaven, R.L. (Box 67)
  - Weiss, John, 18l8-l879 (Box 67)
  - Wlechman (Box 67)
  - Wells, David Ames, 1828-1898 (Box 67)
  - Welton, Mrs. L.A. (Box 67)
  - Wemple, William Y. (Box 67)
  - Weston, Anne Warren, 1853 (Box 67)
  - Weston, Anne Warren, 1854-1959 (Box 68)
  - Weston, Caroline (Box 68)
  - Weston, Deborah (Box 68)
  - Weston, Emma Forbes (Box 68)
  - Weston, Helen (Box 68)
  - Weston, Lucia (Box 68)
  - Weston, R (Box 68)
  - Weston, Richard Warren (Box 68)
  - Wheeler, D.H. (Box 68)
  - White, H.S (Box 68)
  - White, Horace, 1834-1916 (Box 68)
  - White, James T. & Co. (Box 68A)
  - White, James W. (Box 68A)
  - White, Jonathan C. (Box 68A)
  - White, Rhoda S (Mrs. James W.) (Box 68A)
  - White, Richard Grant, 1821-1885 (Box 68A)
  - White, W.A. (Box 68A)
  - Whitmann, Jones (Box 68A)
  - Whitmere, Seth (Box 68A)
  - Whittier, John Greenleaf, 1807-1892 (Box 68A)
  - Wiard, Norman, 1826-1896 (Box 68A)
  - Wickhan, William (Box 68A)
  - Wilcox, Julius (Box 68A)
  - Wilder, J.H. (Box 68A)
  - Wilkinson, Charlotte Mary (Box 68A)
  - Wilkeson, Samuel (Box 68A)
  - Willard, Emma (Box 68A)
  - Willard, Samuel (Box 68A)
  - Willcox, Anna G (Box 69)
  - Willcox, David (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Elizabeth N. (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Frederic A (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Hamilton (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Henry (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Mary Alleyne Otis Gay (Mrs. W.G.) (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Sydney Gay (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Mary (Box 69)
  - Willcox, William G (Box 69)
  - Willcox, William H (Box 69)
  - Willcox, Mrs. William H. (Box 69)
  - Williams, Henry Willard, 1821-1895 (Box 70)
  - Williams, Isaiah Thornton (Box 70)
  - Williams, J.E. (Box 70)
  - Williston, H.C. (Box 70)
  - Wilson, Alexander (Box 70)
  - Wilson, Henry, 1812-1875 (Box 70)
  - Wilson, Henry J. (Box 70)
  - Winser, Erastus (Box 70)
  - Winslow, Abby Gay (Mrs. Isaac) (Box 70)
  - Winslow, Frances (Box 70)
  - Winslow, Isaac (Box 70)
  - Winslow, Jeremiah (Box 71)
  - Winslow, Joshua (Box 71)
  - Winsor, Justin, 1831-1897 (Box 71)
  - Winthrop, William, 1831-1899 (Box 71)
  - Wood, Fernando, 18l2-l88l (Box 71)
  - Woodberry, George (Box 71)
  - Woodruff, A.B. (Box 71)
  - Woodruff, J.B. (Box 71)
  - Woods, J.O. (Box 71)
  - Wool, John Ellis, 1784-1869 (Box 71)
  - Wright, Anna E. Harris (Box 71)
  - Wright, Edward N. (Box 71)
  - Wright, Henry Clarke (Box 71)
  - Wright, Jane (Box 71)
  - Wright, Paulina S (Box 71)
  - Wyman, Emm E (Box 71)
  - Wyman, Emma (Willard) (Box 71)
  - Wyman, John (Box 71)
  - Y., Deborah (Box 71)
  - Young, Charles P. (Box 71)
  - Young, Francis G (Box 71)
  - Young, John Russell (Box 71)
- Series II: Manuscripts and Documents
  - A to G (Box 72)
  - Gay, S.H.: A-C (Box 73)
  - Gay, S.H.: C-P (Box 74)
  - Gay, Winkworth – Lowell, J.S. (Box 75)
  - Gay, Sydney Howard. Record of fugitives [slaves], v.p., 1855-1858. 2 vol. (in bound notebooks) (Box 75)
  - Macarty – Winslow & miscellaneous (Box 76)
  - Genealogical materials (Box 77)
- Series III: Photographs
  - Photographs (Box 77)
- Series IV: Printed Materials
  - Printed materials (Box 78)
  - Printed materials -- Books (Box 79)